[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "CD", ",", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "So what do you think went wrong here?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "do", "you", "think", "went", "wrong", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "Well, Piers, number one, thank you for having me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "number", "one", ",", "thank", "you", "for", "having", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "What did you feel when you watched those images?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "watched", "those", "images", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Well, I felt a huge disappointment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "felt", "a", "huge", "disappointment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Or should she be allowed to lead the life she wants to lead?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "should", "she", "be", "allowed", "to", "lead", "the", "life", "she", "wants", "to", "lead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Of course she should lead the life she wants to lead.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "she", "should", "lead", "the", "life", "she", "wants", "to", "lead", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ":", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "It means that public opinion had been driven I think by the saturation coverage on television and all of the commentary, so that most people were directed to believe -- and, you know, I'm sure you wouldn't deny the fact you were directing people to think this -- that this woman killed her child.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "means", "that", "public", "opinion", "had", "been", "driven", "I", "think", "by", "the", "saturation", "coverage", "on", "television", "and", "all", "of", "the", "commentary", ",", "so", "that", "most", "people", "were", "directed", "to", "believe", "--", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", "you", "would", "n't", "deny", "the", "fact", "you", "were", "directing", "people", "to", "think", "this", "--", "that", "this", "woman", "killed", "her", "child", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Jealous?", "question_tokens": ["Jealous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Tell me about the -- I also love the fact that even then you could tell that you had this kind of firebrand attitude.", "answer_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "the", "--", "I", "also", "love", "the", "fact", "that", "even", "then", "you", "could", "tell", "that", "you", "had", "this", "kind", "of", "firebrand", "attitude", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Was it as simple as that?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "as", "simple", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "You know, Piers, it's so complicated.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "so", "complicated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "When you get criticized, what do you think is the biggest misconception about you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "get", "criticized", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "is", "the", "biggest", "misconception", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Oh, Piers, come on, you've been through this, I'm sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "Piers", ",", "come", "on", ",", "you", "'ve", "been", "through", "this", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "How has it come to this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "has", "it", "come", "to", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "POS", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "How did you feel when your wife said this to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "your", "wife", "said", "this", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think you need to remember, too, that she is, from time to time, what's called a blackout drunk.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "you", "need", "to", "remember", ",", "too", ",", "that", "she", "is", ",", "from", "time", "to", "time", ",", "what", "'s", "called", "a", "blackout", "drunk", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What do you hope to achieve by speaking publicly about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "hope", "to", "achieve", "by", "speaking", "publicly", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, I'll tell you a few things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "a", "few", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Is this a short, sharp, shock treatment that you have implemented here?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "a", "short", ",", "sharp", ",", "shock", "treatment", "that", "you", "have", "implemented", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I won't rule any of those things out right now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wo", "n't", "rule", "any", "of", "those", "things", "out", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "What is it that you say that keeps you all going?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "that", "you", "say", "that", "keeps", "you", "all", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I think that we have certain things that were instilled in us from my mother and my father as we grew up.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "have", "certain", "things", "that", "were", "instilled", "in", "us", "from", "my", "mother", "and", "my", "father", "as", "we", "grew", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Billy"]}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Now, who are you closest to, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "who", "are", "you", "closest", "to", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "TO", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "I would say I'm closest to Billy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "I", "'m", "closest", "to", "Billy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Do you think he's serious about this kind of stuff?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "serious", "about", "this", "kind", "of", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "I think that you have been caught in the -- like many other people, in this web, because I think it has always been a plan of his.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "you", "have", "been", "caught", "in", "the", "--", "like", "many", "other", "people", ",", "in", "this", "web", ",", "because", "I", "think", "it", "has", "always", "been", "a", "plan", "of", "his", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "It's all about you, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "about", "you", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Of course, at the end of the day.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]